Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
LA'AN: Previously on
Star Trek Strange New Worlds...
All my life.
I've hated Augments.
The damage they did.
They almost destroyed Earth.
BATEL: You have
a very unique last name.
Do you have any relation
to Khan Noonien Singh?
Yes.
"You're an abomination. an Augment."
That's what the other kids called me
when they heard my name.
"Augment monster!"
NEERA: Genetics is not destiny.
despite what you may have been taught.
You were not born a monster.
You were just born with
the capacity for actions.
good or ill.
LA'AN: Security Officer's Log.
Stardate 1581.2.
Nobody told me
when I took this assignment
just how many friends
it would make for me.
The ring was a gift from my matriarch.
The transporter buffer
doesn't steal from people.
Okay. That's enough. Thank you.
LA'AN: It is a well-known fact
that people love it
when you bring them bad news.
May I inquire as to who filed
this noise complaint against me?
It was anonymous.
I shall make every effort
to practice less vigorously
going forward.
LA'AN: And. quite frankly.
who doesn't find having
their belongings searched endearing?
By "suspicious provenance"
you're implying
that I stole these artifacts?
"Property of
the Archeology Department."
I used to work there. didn't I?
So this is all aboveboard.
Once you have lived through
every natural disaster
and economic calamity in human history
without becoming a pack rat.
then you can judge me.
I still have a bunker in Vermont.
where I used to live.
in case this whole
"no money. socialist utopia" thing
turns out to be a fad.
Yes. well. and that's a fake.
so you can tell the Louvre
to stop calling me!
You can take it up with Captain Pike.
(GRUNTING)
Easy.
You are going to take my head off.
- As your physician. I'd advi...
- You're not here as my physician.
Well. as your sparring partner.
I'd advise you talk to your physician.
Maybe he could help...
I don't need to talk. okay?
I don't need to be medicated.
You didn't come to the party for Una
at the captain's quarters.
(YELLS)
What was that?
I simply used your energy against you.
Trying to bear
all of this by yourself.
- it's got to be...
- What?
Lonely.
It doesn't need to be.
I'll see you tomorrow.
WOMAN: (ON PA) Attention 2-4.
Attention. Bay 2-4.
maintain tactical...
(WHOOSHING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
Who are you? How did you get aboard?
Help.
LA'AN: That's not from a phaser.
It's from a bullet.
There's been an attack. In the past.
You have to stop it.
(GRUNTING AND PANTING)
You need to get to the bridge.
(ALARM BLARING)
Captain. I need to...
...talk to you?
Ma'am. not to be impolite.
but who are you
and what the hell
are you doing on my ship?
PIKE: Space.
The final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the starship Enterprise.
Its five-year mission.
to explore strange new worlds...
to seek out new life
and new civilizations.
to boldly go
where no one has gone before.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Captain. incoming hail
from the Vulcan ship.
On viewer.
I'm Captain James Kirk
of the United Earth Fleet
ship Enterprise.
You've violated
our sovereign territory.
State your intentions.
I am Spock. captain of the Sh'Rel.
I am here to formally request
your assistance.
Our war with
the Romulan Star Empire has been...
Disastrous. We're aware.
It is a human adage. I believe.
that the enemy of your enemy
is your friend.
Maybe in some other lifetime.
Captain Spock.
We have our own problems with Romulus
and we can't afford
to fight a war on two fronts.
Without your assistance.
the last of our fleet
will be destroyed.
Our home world
will be left defenseless.
I'm sorry. I wish there was
something we could do.
Captain. I think it's best
we have a discussion in private.
So you're telling me that
there's an alternate timeline
where I'm not
the captain of this ship?
All I know is that ten minutes ago.
I was on my ship with
my captain and now I'm here.
And everything's changed.
Yes.
Our scientists have theorized that
such a thing could be possible.
A far simpler explanation
is you've lost your mind.
Except there's no record of you
in our database.
Because this isn't my Enterprise.
It certainly is not.
But it's supposed to be.
I guess the man I spoke to was right.
There was some kind of attack.
Something in the past changed.
which would mean that
my reality is gone.
But you can't tell me
what changed or when.
Or why.
Except that it's the work of
some kind of time-traveling assassin?
Someone shot the man
before he gave me this.
It must be the reason
why I'm still here.
why I remember my own timeline.
- Can we use it to send you back?
- No. I told you.
I'm pretty sure there's
nothing for me to go back to.
My timeline doesn't exist
unless I can stop this attack.
Well. you're asking me
to take an awful lot on faith.
- I am.
- Neither of us has any idea
what that device really does.
It could be a weapon.
The man told me to get to the bridge.
I think you're supposed to help me.
Starfleet has regulations
for situations like this.
I have to stop you there. ma'am.
I have never heard of this Starfleet.
I am a captain
in the United Earth Fleet.
And you are a guest.
an intruder. really.
on my ship.
I need you to hand that over.
My science officer and chief engineer
will study it and report it
back to UEF Command.
No.
- (SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
- (TRAFFIC NOISES IN DISTANCE)
Wait!
You got to be kidding me.
- Did you break it?
- Did I break it?
No. it's just not programmed correctly
or out of energy. maybe.
Or it's put us
where we're supposed to be
and doesn't want us to leave.
I have to get back to my ship.
My God. what have you done?
Oh. I'm sorry.
but this was done to me
just as much as it was done to you.
So we can stand here
and argue about it
or we can try and figure out a plan.
There is going to be an attack.
It's going to change the timeline.
We have to stop it.
Do you have a tricorder?
No. Or a communicator
or a phaser. Thanks for that.
Right. well we'll have to have
a look around then. won't we?
Thank you.
Seems to be New York City.
Mid-21st century.
- What?
It's Toronto.
The biggest city in what
used to be called Canada?
You know. maple leaves.
politeness. poutine.
I take it you've never been.
I've never been to Earth at all.
I was born in space
on the U.S.S. Iowa.
Earth in my time isn't like this.
What is it like?
A battleground for a while.
then occupied territory
and then a ruin.
Oh. God!
Was it always this freezing on Earth?
This isn't actually
that bad for Canada.
But it will get colder at night.
We need to change before we freeze.
Come on.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Never seen a revolving door before?
I'm from space.
Find an outfit.
There's changing rooms over there.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- Hmm.
- Huh.
What do you think?
It's fine.
Grab your clothes.
LA'AN: Ah.
- They're going to expect us to...
- I know.
You a fast runner?
(CASHIER CHUCKLES)
I have a better idea. Hold that.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Ma'am. can you step to the side?
WOMAN: Sorry. This still has
a tag on it. here.
We can't do that again.
People during this time
traded currency for everything.
Housing. food...
All right. so let's get some currency.
What kind of marketable
21st century skills do you have?
You know what?
Give me a few minutes.
(SINGING) We had to find our way back
To the place with the morning sun
Ain't no doubt. ain't no mistake
'Cause we got it all in hand
We got it all in hand
The time is right
To claim my stake
So. come on
And this is it
This is what we got going
People. get ready to feel
This is it
This is what we got going
- People. get ready to feel
- People. get ready
This is it
This is what we got going
People. get ready to feel
Don't take this the wrong way. but...
What. I don't seem like
a "thinking five steps ahead"
kind of guy?
- Mmm-mmm.
- (CHUCKLES)
I used to play all the time
with my first officer.
till she got sick of losing.
Been looking
for a proper opponent ever since.
That old-fashioned.
two-dimensional version. though.
it's basically idiot's chess.
Ooh.
Come on.
Hi. Two. please.
MAN: Yeah. sure thing.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Mmm-mmm.
Come on.
I am your superior officer.
and I am ordering you
to have a hot dog.
You don't work for Starfleet.
so you can't order me to do anything.
We need to be looking of
some sign of what's changed
or who changed it.
With what to go on?
Why this day? Why us?
Why here?
Nothing seems threatening.
It's all just sort of. I don't know.
pleasant.
I know. It's terrible.
You know what I mean. I just...
But we were sent back
for a reason. so...
(CLEARS THROAT)
- LA'AN: What?
- Nothing.
You don't have sunsets in your time?
From the videos I've seen.
we mostly have
clouds of ash that won't clear
for a thousand years
and underground lunar habitats
with no view of the sun at all.
My advice...
Don't skip good hot dogs
when you can get them.
Fine.
We eat. we find
some place to warm up. then...
Yeah. yeah. yeah. we do your thing.
Yeah.
Mmm!
(MOUTH FULL) I'm gonna go back
and get one more.
Ah!
Oof!
Well. that really
beats a sonic shower.
What are you doing?
Trying to remember
21st century history.
You should write a list
of what you remember. too.
We can figure out what's changed.
When there's a tiny little bar
to go through?
Are you serious?
We may not have much time.
Not much time?
I may have missed
a few lectures in temporal mechanics.
but I understand enough
to know what you're asking me to do.
This is a fork in the road.
Your future and mine
diverging from this moment.
If we fix your timeline.
we destroy mine.
My life. my friends.
my whole existence erased.
I'm sorry. but your timeline
- isn't supposed to exist.
- According to who?
My best option
is to do absolutely nothing.
Enjoy the hot dogs and the hot showers
and let whatever's gonna happen happen
and then figure out
how I can get back home.
I've seen your timeline.
You're at war. Your Earth is a ruin.
We've made the stars our home.
The Moon. Mars.
- Venus. Europa.
- In my timeline.
humanity has spread across
dozens of worlds.
We're part of a federation of species.
We don't need anyone else's
help to survive.
And just surviving
is good enough for you?
Oh. and I suppose you come from
some sort of a utopia.
My Earth still has sunsets.
Okay. yes. our 21st century.
it got bad.
But after the first contact
with the Vulcans.
our Earth became a paradise.
The Federation and Starfleet
are forces for good.
not just on Earth
but throughout the entire galaxy.
You're a soldier fighting a war
it seems like you've already lost...
We're not out of the fight yet.
...when you could be an explorer.
Or...
I may not exist
in your timeline at all.
But you do.
I mean. we've never met. but
I've heard stories about you
from your brother.
Sam's alive?
(EXPLOSION)
My God.
"Get to the bridge."
It's been about an hour since
we first learned of the explosion...
The bridge explosion.
all of this is familiar.
I think it happened in my timeline.
Mine. too.
One of the longest bridges
in the world destroyed
just after it was completed.
That means this can't be the attack
that he was talking about.
This isn't the moment things changed.
Wait. look over there.
Do you see that?
- See what?
- The wreckage.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Can I see the photos you just took?
Please.
She meant to say please.
Right. that right there.
Does this get bigger?
Like. you want me to zoom in?
Right. Zoom in.
Is something wrong?
No. Thank you.
That charring. I've seen it before.
- It's a photonic bomb.
- Photonic?
They're not supposed
to develop that technology
for at least a hundred years.
The kind of technology
a time-traveling assassin might use?
Except. if our memories are correct.
this was already supposed to happen.
They're removing the evidence.
Come on. we need to follow them.
We'll never keep up on foot. Come on.
Hey.
Most vehicles have
private ownership in this time.
Oh. I know.
Where did you learn to do that?
Spent six months
in a Denobulan prison.
Cellmate was a Vulcan.
I can also make Plomeek soup
in the toilet.
There. There. there. there.
Go. go. go.
Yeah. I'm trying.
(ENGINE STARTS)
There it is.
- Slow down.
- I'm slowing.
Be discreet.
Basically my middle name.
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- Whoa. whoa. whoa.
No. actually.
I've read your personnel file.
- You have some insane...
- No. Tiberius is not insane.
The least discreet middle name.
It was my grandfather's.
What's your brother's?
Sam Aurelius Augustus Benedictus Kirk?
Sam is his middle name.
Most people call him George.
Absolutely no one calls him George.
Tiberius and Sam.
- Your parents must really hate you.
- You're one to talk.
La'An Noonien-Soong.
- Singh.
- Whatever.
You haven't heard it before.
What?
Just the first time in a while
someone hasn't recognized it.
Famous?
Infamous is more like it.
Oh.
OFFICER: Hey!
Damn it.
(SINGING) K-Hole at the Dali
Seeing the unknown
Well. I might have been on molly
'Cause my mind's being blown...
Hold on.
To the next floor
Such a strong sedater...
No. you don't actually have to...
You literally just told me to hold on.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa!
- That was a person.
- All right.
Well. actually. keep holding on.
It's a total light picture
Kaleidoscope
You turn around
And you don't know where you been
You look up at the glass dome
And the room begins to spin
Let's go out and find the ocean
'Cause I think we need a swim
Turn around. start it over
Let's begin
In the K-Hole at the Dali
(SIREN WAILING)
Well. I might have been on molly
'Cause my mind's being blown
You turn around
And you don't know where you been
You look up at the glass dome
And the room begins to spin
Let's go out and find the ocean
'Cause I think we need a swim
Turn around
Start it over
Let's begin
I really don't know
what the problem is.
Where are you taking him?
What are you charging him with?
Driving without a license.
failure to follow traffic laws.
No. I told you my license
is in my other pants.
I'll be fine. just see if you
can pick up on their trail.
What trail?
What an incredible surprise.
Let me guess. you haven't made
your quota for the week yet?
Move along. ma'am.
Just so you're aware.
this is streaming live.
Say hello to the entire
very judgmental Internet.
Are your cameras active for the stop?
No?
Did you stop this man
because you were profiling him
for being American?
This is a totally routine stop.
Sure. you just randomly pulled over
a famous civil rights attorney.
Nothing random about it.
So you agree.
this is targeted harassment.
Did you stop the doctor
because of his work
defending victims of tyrannical
law enforcement overreach
or is it because of the op-ed
he published in The Atlantic
- about breaking up police unions?
- DISPATCHER: Backup required
- at bridge bombing site.
- Copy. Dispatch.
All right. we're gonna
let you go with a warning.
This time.
Drive more carefully in the future.
What the hell was that?
I have no idea.
Thanks.
Yeah. no problem.
Sera.
Vanessa.
Jim.
You know I'm not
a civil rights attorney.
Totally.
Then why did you...
'Cause you were following the van.
Without a lot of discretion.
for what it's worth.
Discretion is his middle name.
Wait. you were following them. too?
Well. if you hadn't let them get away.
we could have found out
where they were taking
the evidence from the bombing.
Okay. look. I'm used to
doing this on my own.
but if you have notes
that we can compare...
You know who blew up the bridge?
Well. I can make an educated guess.
I mean. it was destroyed.
obviously not randomly.
because of what it symbolized.
International cooperation.
the world getting smaller.
humanity working together.
They'll blame it on a terrorist attack
and we'll go back
to fighting each other
instead of the real threat.
You mean...
Aliens.
Anyway. it was super fun
saving you from an illegal
black site torture dungeon.
I got to go.
My wife was abducted.
Taken aboard an alien ship.
She saw things.
Yes. I'm his...
I did.
It was terrifying. the things I saw.
Well. like. what did you see?
Advanced technology far beyond
anything humans possess.
What kind of technology?
Something called a photonic bomb.
That's what blew up the bridge.
Have you heard of anything like that?
A lot of crazies
latch onto this stuff.
They're looking for
something to believe in
outside the mainstream. trying to find
the seams in the bunny suit.
Right.
Well. things have been changing.
You have to have noticed. Right?
I mean. there's more attacks
and they're closer together.
Usually the government is better
at covering them up.
To be clear. we're talking about
the government of...
No. no. no.
it's an international cabal.
It's the only thing all of
the governments in the world
can agree on.
Keeping the alien attacks secret
in exchange for
any advanced tech that they recover.
I mean. they have a facility here
where they work on it.
Experimental aircraft.
quantum computers.
I heard that they even have
a cold fusion reactor here in the city
that powers their entire operation.
The bridge was about sowing division.
What about the other attacks?
What was the connection?
Okay. so Chernobyl. Tunguska. JFK.
random gas leak explosions. all of it
is about slowing down human progress.
Keeping us stuck on this rock
so we never go to space.
Are you guys hungry?
'Cause I'm hungry.
I am hungry. actually.
Wait. I...
KIRK: Wait. poutine has gravy?
- This is amazing.
- Can you focus?
I'm not sure we can believe
anything she's telling us.
She knew enough to follow the van
from the bridge explosion.
She's unhinged.
She grew up in a time when everyone
thought aliens were science fiction.
But in her gut
she knows that they're real.
and that they aren't
necessarily friendly.
I mean. that would make anyone
unhinged. right?
Hey. sorry.
This works better with visuals.
I have spent years
collecting these pictures.
I mean. there's plenty available
on the Internet.
but 99% of it is nonsense
and memes. right?
- (WHISPERS) What's a meme?
- I don't know.
SERA: Sorry these are so blurry.
I swear. half of these people
on forums
are still using dial-up.
KIRK: How did you get this?
An astronomer trying to take a picture
of the International Space Station.
In the right place at the right time.
And speaking of.
there's a hookah place
across from the bridge explosion site.
I bought the surveillance
footage off the owner
before the police could confiscate it.
and he was waiting 15 minutes
before the explosion.
And that's one of the guys
who made off with the wreckage.
Like he already knew
it was going to happen.
Well. I'm sorry we didn't
have more to tell you.
We're new at this.
No. I mean. you listened.
You didn't tell me that I was crazy.
You have no idea
what that means to me.
Anyway. thank you.
You have to feel bad for her.
To be so certain of something.
so close to the proof.
Well. she's closer than she thinks.
That ship she showed us?
It's Romulan.
I remember now.
Look. she said that
there's an experimental
cold fusion reactor
somewhere in the city.
Well. I know that there is.
because in a few days
it's gonna be destroyed
and wipe out Toronto.
A Romulan first strike.
None of that happens in my timeline.
Then we need to find
the cold fusion reactor first.
Stop the time traveler
from destroying it.
Which would be trivial
if we had a tricorder.
Yeah.
If only someone hadn't impulsively
zapped us over here without one.
Any chance that same someone
took a lot of engineering
extension courses
at the Academy?
Maybe she can build one for us?
Someone had to audit
the intro course. so...
So I guess we just
need to find an engineer
from the stone ages
- to build us a cold fusion detector.
- Yeah.
Ideally one who's not gonna ask
a lot of follow-up questions.
(REPORTER ON TV
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
LA'AN: Vermont.
I might actually know somebody
in Vermont.
Just trust me.
- PELIA: Ugh! Damn it! (GROANS)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
(SINGSONGY) We're closed.
This is going to sound crazy.
but we spent all day getting here.
We had to bribe a border guard.
we took a cab and four buses.
Please. Pelia.
How do you know my name?
I know you.
And I know your secret.
So. please. open the damn door.
Come on. come on.
PELIA: Look. I have a terrible
memory for faces.
and yours does not ring a bell.
And besides. people don't just
wander in off the street
saying. "I know your secret."
To get a free pass from me.
I need more to go on than that.
How else would I know
that you're a Lanthanite.
an ancient sect of beings
who live impossibly long lives.
who've hidden amongst humans
largely undetected
for thousands of years?
How else could I know that
you stole that
from the Louvre?
How did you find me?
I knew you were at a place called
The Archaeology Department.
But I thought it was
an actual. well. you know.
archaeology department.
So. then we checked out
a lot of universities.
And when that didn't work.
a guy at the Apple Store taught me
how to use DuckDuckGo.
None of that answers
how you know about me
in the first place.
I don't exactly advertise.
We have something in common.
We both have secrets that would topple
a lot of people's firmly-held beliefs.
All I can say is
my friend and I.
we're on a mission
to protect something
beautiful.
The future of humanity.
And I think you know from experience
just how fragile that future is.
We are maybe hours away
from losing that future entirely.
You are the only person
I can trust to help us.
"We both have brain-melting secrets"
is. I guess. a good enough reason
to help someone.
What you need?
An engineer.
Well. then.
why the hell did you come to me?
You're not an engineer?
I work retail.
Does this look like
an engineer's engineering place?
I haven't taken a math class
since Pythagoras made the crap up.
You two are trying to find
a nuclear reactor?
Why is that?
I've had enough bad run-ins
with law enforcement
to last several lifetimes.
And now. this business
with the bridge.
We're the ones trying
to not blow up the reactor.
I guess it doesn't matter much.
I like a good puzzle.
but I don't know what help I can be.
I'm the one that thought
cold fusion was pretend.
like Bigfoot or lasers.
Lasers
are also real.
All right. you know. I can't keep up
with every scientific whatever.
- You let this lady repair my ship?
- Okay. what?
We don't have to understand
how cold fusion works
to find the reactor. we just
need to find its byproducts.
Excess heat. neutrons. tritium.
Tritium. like in divers' watches.
Old divers' watches from the '80s.
I'm gonna show you. Follow me.
I guarantee you
this is going to be insane.
Shh!
PELIA: Here you go.
They light up.
Or they used to.
Something about tritium running out
after about 20 years.
and then they're basically
worthless after that.
LA'AN: Tritium gives off
a small amount of radiation.
The dials must be coated
in something that reacts with it.
Maybe phosphor?
Tritium has a short half-life.
so it would decay.
Leaving only
the reactive material behind.
Which means what? Careful of the...
If we take the glass casing off.
the reactive material
will be exposed to the air.
and if there's tritium present...
The hands of the watch
will glow.
Thank you so much for your help.
You are more of an engineer
than you think.
Thank you.
Maybe I missed my calling.
Be nice to make an honest living
for a change.
Not that any of this stuff is stolen.
KIRK: Wandering for hours. Anything?
I promise I will mention it
if it starts to glow.
Could've just let me wear it. is all.
- That again.
- No. it's a man's watch.
You just want to be in charge.
You know. if I was in your position.
I don't know that I would have
gone along with this.
I don't think I could have
gotten this far without you.
You'd definitely have frozen to death
on the first night.
Or starved.
That hot dog saved your life.
(LAUGHS)
Well. how many people can say that?
I might be the only one.
Truth is.
if we can only save
one timeline. I'd...
I'd rather live in yours.
I mean. I know
that's not how it works.
Like I mentioned.
I missed a few lectures
- in temporal mechanics. but...
- What if you could?
Come to my time.
I'm not sure one timeline
is big enough for two of me.
I'm serious.
I brought you here.
If we can fix this.
maybe the device could
take us both back.
People are
usually
difficult for me.
There's always been a barrier.
and it can get
lonely.
But you...
Me?
I'm special?
(LAUGHS)
Yes.
No.
Both. I guess.
I've been carrying something
around for a long time.
Something in my heritage.
You come from a long line
of ax murderers?
Oh. no. we never use axes.
Truth is. maybe
I'm letting that go now.
And maybe it helps that
you've never even heard
of the scarlet letter
I've worn my whole life.
The Scarlet Letter?
It's a novel by Hawthorne.
It's about a woman who's marked.
like the Mark of Cain.
You've never even...
Yes. I know Hawthorne
and the Old Testament.
I'm just messing with you.
You ass...
- Hey.
- Yeah?
You broke your promise.
We're close.
This must be it.
The cold fusion reactor is in here.
- (LOCK CLICKS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Well. this is your mission.
- What's the play?
- (DOOR CLOSES)
We need to get inside. find out
what we're really dealing with.
All right. So. we wait here.
watch for someone coming or going.
force their hand into the scanner.
We won't need to.
Look at the sign.
"Noonien-Singh."
That can't be a coincidence.
You wanted to know why you were
picked for this mission.
What does it mean? What does
your family have to do with this?
What did they do?
(SCANNER HUMS)
- (LOCK CLICKS)
- It worked.
Marker in my DNA. maybe.
- SERA: Well. this worked out.
- (GUN COCKS)
Thank you for helping me
get into this place.
I'm gonna need both of you
to come with me inside.
Don't.
You're the one
we're looking for. aren't you?
- You're from the future?
- As are you.
You're Captain James T. Kirk.
Embarrassing how long
it took me to recognize you.
Recognize me?
I would say that
your reputation precedes you.
but it's kind of the other way around.
You blew up the bridge.
I didn't.
But everything I told you was true.
My people have been
slowing human progress.
but they should have gone much further
than blowing up
a couple of labs and bridges.
They have no idea
how troublesome humanity becomes.
Your people.
You're a Romulan from the future.
A hell of a job on the disguise.
Still not quite used to the ears yet.
- Now get in.
- Not a chance.
You want to shoot us? Go ahead.
You have to know that if you do.
the building's alarms will go off.
Security will lock the place down.
your plan will fail.
You're bluffing.
Try me.
- (GRUNTS)
- LA'AN: No.
No.
No. no...
You're gonna be okay.
(ALARM BLARING)
Not bluffing.
No. you're gonna be okay. Look at me.
It's okay.
Keep your eyes on me.
Say hi to Sam for me.
No.
No. no. James.
(ECHOING) James.
(MUFFLED) James.
SERA: Okay.
a little impulsive on my part.
But maybe worth it
to be the one to kill James T. Kirk.
(GRUNTS)
(LOCK CLICKS)
WOMAN: (ON PA) Attention.
security breach in progress.
MAN: Freeze!
Stop!
(GRUNTS)
Attention. security breach
in progress.
Security to the reactor.
Security won't let you
get to the reactor.
I'm not going to the reactor.
What?
The reactor exploding.
destroying the city.
that's what changes.
Well. that was Plan A.
But if you can't use a hand grenade
you should use a scalpel.
Open it.
Use your handprint to open the door.
No.
You know who's in there. right?
You're here to kill
Khan Noonien Singh.
Why?
Because a computer simulation
told me to.
You can't be serious.
Time is like a black box.
It's too complicated
to leave to intuition.
so we built computers
that will tell us the results
of certain changes.
And this was your answer?
Khan becomes a brutal tyrant.
I mean. maybe humanity needs
the dark age that he brings in
to usher in
their age of enlightenment.
Or maybe it's just random.
Doesn't really matter. though.
'cause if I kill him.
the Federation never forms.
and the Romulans
lose their greatest adversary.
But. you know. so many people
have tried to influence these events.
you know. to delay them or stop them.
I mean. whole temporal wars
have been fought over them.
And it's almost as if
time itself is pushing back.
and events reinsert themselves.
And all this was supposed
to happen back in 1992.
and I've been trapped here
for 30 years
trying to get my shot at him.
I'm not gonna stop now.
So open the door.
My real name
is La'An Noonien-Singh.
My ancestor is Khan Noonien Singh.
And his legacy is genocide.
torture.
and me.
You have a device in your pocket
that protects you from changes
in the timeline.
If he dies.
you can live whatever
kind of life you want.
and you'll never
have to hear the name Khan
ever again.
You can be free of him.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(ALARM CONTINUES
BLARING IN DISTANCE)
CHILD: Are you gonna kill me?
No. of course not. I...
(PUTS DOWN GUN)
You don't need to be scared of me.
Come here.
You're just a little boy.
Are you alone
or are there others like you?
Are you here to take me away?
This won't make any sense right now.
Maybe it won't ever.
But you are right
where you need to be.
GUARD: Got a man down!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
PELIA: Perhaps I'll just mail it.
Really doesn't matter
what the bulletin says.
the statute of limitations
passed decades ago.
I checked.
UNA: Is there a statute of limitations
on plundering antiquities?
Oh. La'An.
Maybe Starfleet Security
wants to weigh in on this.
I'd
say we should
let this one slide. Captain.
You're not wearing your uniform.
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong. Captain.
I just needed to check on something.
and now I have.
Excuse me.
La'An Noonien-Singh. I'm Agent Ymalay
from the Department
of Temporal Investigations.
Am I meant to know what that is?
A division of the Federation
that investigates and repairs
damage to the timeline.
You haven't heard of us
because we don't exist yet.
The man who gave me this...
Was one of us.
Thank you again
for completing his mission.
It must have been harrowing.
I have to insist that you not share
any of what you experienced.
even with Captain Pike.
or anyone else from this time.
You sent me back
to protect a mass murderer?
To be clear.
I didn't send you anywhere.
I had to kill to protect him.
I had to watch my f...
And I can't even talk about it?
Those events were never
supposed to happen.
and you were never meant
to be aware of them.
Neither was your companion.
You protected the timeline
in a way no one else could have.
Would you risk
undoing all of that?
No.
Thank you again for your assistance.
And. if you could.
return our equipment.
(LINE RINGING)
This is Lieutenant Kirk.
Hi.
Do I know you?
No. we've never met.
I'm La'An Noonien-Singh.
Chief of Security on the Enterprise.
Oh. God. What did Sam do?
Oh. no. no. Sam... Sorry. Sam's fine.
Sorry to worry you.
I was just looking for a...
Something for his file.
His security file?
That's right. Just a place
of birth. please.
Riverside. Iowa. Same as me.
Iowa on Earth?
Iowa on Earth. Yes. ma'am.
Is that really why you're calling?
That's it. I'm just
a stickler for an orderly
security record. so...
Well. if you want
the real dirt on George Samuel Kirk.
buy me a drink next time
we're on starbase together.
I got some real gems
for his permanent file.
That sounds lovely.
Kirk out.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm